Finding Aid for Shirley Wheeler Smith Papers, 1881-1959
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Shirley Wheeler Smith Papers 1881-1959
Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.
86711 Aa 2; UAm
Vice-president and secretary of the University of Michigan; correspondence; research materials for his biographies of university presidents; files relating to activities on the Ann Arbor City Council; course notes from classes at the University of Michigan; and photographs.
15 linear feet
1 oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Shirley Wheeler Smith (donor no. 1718 ) and his estate (donor no. 3657 ). The bulk of the material came from the estate in 1960 and 1965.
The collection is open to research.
Shirley Wheeler Smith was born May 3, 1875 in Nashville, Michigan. He graduated from the University of Michigan in 1897. He was an instructor in English from 1898 to 1901 at which time he was appointed secretary of the Michigan Alumni Association and editor of the Michigan Alumnus. He was named secretary of the University of Michigan by the Board of Regents in 1908 after working for four years as assistant in the president's office of the Fidelity Mutual Life Insurance Co. In 1927, Smith became secretary and business manager combined. In the 1930 administrative reorganization of the University, Smith was named vice-president and secretary, in which position he supervised all of the financial and business affairs of the University. He retired in 1945 devoting himself to scholarly interests that included biographies of U-M presidents James B. Angell and Harry B. Hutchins.
The Shirley Wheeler Smith papers include a combination of personal and professional materials. Much of Smith's career with the U-M is documented in the official records of the University, most notably in the records of the Secretary's Office and the papers of the presidents under whom he served (Angell, Hutchins, Burton, Little, and Ruthven). Even so, these papers contain much material relating to the business affairs of the U-M. The extensive correspondence files (with partial index) demonstrate wide influence in all phases of University operations as he corresponded with presidents, faculty, members of the board of regents, and other university personnel. Also documented in the collection is Smith's activities with the city of Ann Arbor and with other community organizations.
The collection has been arranged into the following series: Correspondence; Research for writings; Topical files; Ann Arbor City Council; Papers (by date); Personal and miscellaneous; and Photographs.
Subjects:
Adams, Henry Carter, 1851-1921.; Ann Arbor (Mich.); Bicycle touring--Europe.; Cooley, Charles Horton, 1864-1929.; Europe--Description and travel.; Hinsdale, B. A. (Burke Aaron), 1837-1900.; Hudson, Richard, 1845-1915.; McLouth, Lawrence Amos, 1863-1927.; Poultry.; Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.; Voyages and travels.; Travelers.; University of Michigan--Administration.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Economics.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Germanic Languages and Literatures.; University of Michigan. Dept. of History.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Philosophy.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Political Science.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Sociology.; University of Michigan--Faculty.; University of Michigan. School of Education.; University of Michigan. Secretary.; University of Michigan--Student notebooks.; University of Michigan. Vice President and Secretary.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Industries--Michigan--Hastings.; Hastings Wool Boot Company.; Industry--Michigan--Hastings--1891-1900.; Laborers--1891-1900.; Michiganensian.; Railroad locomotives.; Smith, Sara Browne.; Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.; University of Michigan--Students--1891-1900.
Contributors:
Abbot, Waldo, 1888-; Adams, James P. (James Pickwell), 1895-1969.; Adams, Randolph Greenfield, 1892-1951.; Ainsworth, Arthur Sardius, 1862-; Alger, Frederick Moulton, 1907-1967.; Allen, Frederick Lewis, 1890-1954.; Anderson, Clinton Presba, 1895-1975; Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Angell, James Rowland, 1869-1949.; Angell, Robert Cooley, 1899-1984; Anspach, Charles Le Roy, 1895-; Artiaga, Santiago, 1878-1962.; Backus, Standish.; Bacon, Mark Reeves, 1852-1941.; Baird, Charles, 1870-1944.; Baits, Vera Burridge, 1892-1963.; Bald, F. Clever (Frederick Clever), 1897-1970.; Bates, Henry Moore, 1869-1949.; Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.; Bingay, Malcolm Wallace, 1884-; Bishop, William Warner, 1871-1955.; Boak, Arthur Edward Romilly, 1888-1962.; Bonisteel, Roscoe O. (Roscoe Osmond), b. 1888.; Boyles, Emerson R., 1881-1960.; Bromage, Arthur W. (Arthur Watson), 1904-1979.; Brown, Prentiss M. (Prentiss Marsh), 1889-1973.; Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.; Brumm, John Lewis, 1878-1958.; Bulkley, Harry C. (Harry Conant), b. 1870.; Burke, Edward R. (Edward Raymond), 1880-1968; Burke, George James, 1885-1950.; Burton, Clarence Monroe, 1853-1932.; Burton, Marion Le Roy, 1874-1925.; Carey, Henry Westronae, 1850-1911.; Chandler, George Moseley.; Clements, William L. (William Lawrence), 1861-1934.; Coller, Frederick A.; Cook, Marshall L., 1858-1955.; Cooley, Mortimer E. (Mortimer Elwyn), 1855-1944.; Cowling, Donald J.; Craig, James Alexander, 1855-1932.; Craig, Robert, 1882-1962.; Cross, Arthur Lyon, 1873-1940.; Curtiss, Mary Louise Welton.; Davis, Calvin Olin, 1871-; Davis, Joseph Baker, 1845-1920.; Day, Edmund Ezra, 1883-1951.; DeFoe, Murl Holcomb, 1879-; Demmon, Isaac Newton, 1842-1920.; Densmore, Gail Ernest, 1894-; Doan, Leland Ira, 1894-1974.; Dolph, Ray A.; Douglas, Lloyd C. (Lloyd Cassel), 1877-1951.; Dumond, Dwight Lowell, 1895-1976; Eccles, Marriner S. (Marriner Stoddard), 1890-1977.; Effinger, John Robert, 1869-1933.; Elliott, Eugene Bradley, 1896-; Emmons, H. H. (Harry H.); Engel, Albert Joseph, 1888-1959.; Fairlie, John A. (John Archibald), 1872-1947.; Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.; Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.; Fitzpatrick, Keene, 1865-1944.; Ford, Edsel, 1893-1943.; Fosdick, Harry Emerson, 1878-1969.; Foss, Sam Walter, 1858-1911.; Frank, Coleman Dudley, 1876-1954.; Frayer, William Alley.; Fuller, Oramel B., b. 1858.; Furstenberg, Albert Carl, 1890-1969.; Gayley, Charles Mills, 1858-1932.; George, Walter F. (Walter Franklin), 1878-1957.; Goddard, Edwin C. (Edwin Charles), 1865-1942.; Gomberg, Moses, 1866-1947.; Goodrich, Francis Lee Dewey, 1877-1962.; Gore, Victor M.; Graham, Frank Porter, 1886-1972; Grant, Claudius Buchanan, 1835-1921.; Green, Fred W. (Fred Warren), 1872-1936.; Griffin, Clare E. (Clare Elmer), 1892-1979; Groesbeck, Alexander J. (Alexander Joseph), 1873-1953.; Guest, Edgar A. (Edgar Albert), 1881-1959.; Haber, William, 1899-1988.; Hanchett, Benjamin Sawtell, 1868-1933.; Harriman, Karl Edwin, 1875-1935.; Hatcher, Harlan, 1898-1998.; Hayden, Joseph Ralston, 1887-1945.; Haynes, Harley Armand, 1875-; Henderson, William D., b. 1866.; Herbert, J. Joseph, 1894-1956.; Hinsdale, W. B. (Wilbert B.), 1851-1944.; Hoad, William Christian, 1874-1962.; Hobbs, William Herbert, 1864-1952.; Hodges, Fred Jenner, 1895-; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; Hubbard, Lucius L. (Lucius Lee), 1849-1933.; Hussey, William Joseph, 1862-1926.; Hutchins, Harry B. (Harry Burns), 1847-1930.; Hutchins, Harry Crocker, 1880-1948.; Iden, Thomas Medary, 1856-1933.; Jones, Samuel Arthur, 1834-1912.; Keatley, Vivien B. (Vivien Bulloch), 1909-; Kelly, Harry F. (Harry Francis), 1895-1971.; Kemp, Edward Gearing, 1887-1962.; Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.; Knutson, Harold, 1880-1963.; Lane, Victor Hugo, 1852-1930.; Lawrence, David Leo, 1889-1966.; Leland, Frank Bruce.; Little, Clarence C. (Clarence Cook), b. 1888.; Lloyd, Alice Crocker, 1893-1950.; Lombard, Warren P. (Warren Plimpton), 1855-1939.; Lorch, Emil, 1870-1963.; McCallum, George P. (George Porterfield), 1871-1952.; McClure, Harry H.; MacLachlan, James Angell, 1891-1967; McLaughlin, Andrew Cunningham, 1861-1947.; McPeek, Russell Roy, 1862-1945.; Maddy, Joseph E. (Joseph Edgar), 1891-1966.; Markley, Mary Elizabeth B., 1864-1956.; Mattern, David Earl, 1890-1959.; Meader, George, 1907-1994; Mechem, Floyd R. (Floyd Russell), 1858-1928.; Michener, Earl C. (Earl Cory), 1876-1957.; Moffit, John Ted, 1862-1947.; Moore, Earl Vincent, 1890-1987.; Morrill, J. L. (James Lewis), 1891-1979; Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.; Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.; Nelson, J. Raleigh (Joseph Raleigh); Newcombe, Frederick Charles, 1858-1927.; Newkirk, Henry Wirt, 1854-1946.; Novy, Frederick George, 1864-1957.; Okkelberg, Peter Olaus, 1880-; Orr, H. Winnett (Hiram Winnett), 1877-1956.; Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860.; Otis, Robert Burns, 1879-; Parker, Edward Foster.; Patterson, Robert Porter, 1891-1952.; Patton, Carl S. (Carl Safford), 1866-1939.; Perkins, John A. (John Alanson), 1914-1982; Peterson, Reuben, 1862-1942.; Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943.; Pillsbury, W. B. (Walter Bowers), 1872-1960.; Pollock, James K. (James Kerr), 1898-1968; Potter, Louise, 1895-; Power, Eugene B., 1905-; Reeves, Jesse Siddall, 1872-1942; Reichert, Rudolph Edward, 1887-1965.; Reisler, Joseph T.; Rice, Warner Grenelle, 1899-; Riggs, Henry Earle, b. 1865.; Robertson, James H. (James Holman), 1915-; Rolfe, John Carew, 1859-1943.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-1971.; Sample, George Washington, 1868-1945.; Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931.; Scott, Fred Newton, 1860-1931.; Scott, Georgia Jackson.; Shaw, Wilfred Byron, 1881-1959.; Shields, Edmund Claude, 1871-1947.; Shorts, Robert P. (Robert Perry), 1879-1975; Sigler, Kim, b. 1894.; Sink, Charles A. (Charles Albert), 1879-1972.; Slossen, Preston William, 1892-; Smith, Clement McDonald, 1844-1923.; Smith, Elbert V., 1864-; Smith, Richard Root, 1869-1940.; Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.; Spill, William Ambrose, 1876-; Sproul, Robert Gordon, 1891-1975.; Staebler, Edward William, 1872-1946.; Staebler, Neil, 1905-2000; Stanley, Albert A. (Albert Augustus), 1851-1932.; Starr, Floyd Elliot, 1883-1980.; Stason, E. Blythe (Edwin Blythe), 1891-1972.; Stone, Ralph, 1868-1956.; Strauss, Louis Abraham, 1872-1938.; Sullivan, Mark, 1874-1952.; Summerfield, Arthur Ellsworth, 1899-1972.; Sundwall, John, 1880-1950.; Tapping, Theodore Hawley, 1889-1969.; Tarbell, Ida M. (Ida Minerva), 1857-1944.; Taylor, F. M. (Fred Manville), 1855-1932.; Thieme, Hugo P. (Hugo Paul), 1870-1940.; Townsend, Charles E. (Charles Elroy), 1856-1924.; Trueblood, Thomas C. (Thomas Clarkson), 1856-1951.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.; Vander Velde, Lewis G. (Lewis George), 1890-1975.; Van Tyne, Claude Halstead, 1869-1930.; Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-; Van Zile, Philip T. (Philip Taylor), 1843-1917.; Voorhies, Paul Warren, 1875-1952.; Walter, Erich Albert.; Ward, Marcus Llewellyn, 1875-1963.; Weissert, Charles Adam, 1878-1947.; Wells, Carlton F. (Carlton Frank), 1898-; Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.; White, Alfred H. (Alfred Holmes), b. 1873.; White, Lee A., b. 1886.; Whitney, Allen Sisson, 1857-1944.; Whitney, Caspar, 1862-1929.; Wiley, Merlin, 1875-; Winter, John Garrett, 1881-1956.; Wrentmore, Clarence George, 1867-1934.; Wriston, Henry M. (Henry Merritt), 1889-1978; Yost, Eunice Josephine Fite, 1881-1975.
Genre Terms:
Cartoons.; Diaries.; Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
- Correspondence
  - 1876-1913, 29 folders (Box 1)
  - 1916-1930, 31 folders (Box 2)
  - 1931-June 1934, 31 folders (Box 3)
  - July 1934-August 1936, 28 folders (Box 4)
  - September 1936-April 1939, 35 folders (Box 5)
  - May 1939-1941, 34 folders (Box 6)
  - 1942-October 1944, 37 folders (Box 7)
  - November 1944-June 1947, 35 folders (Box 8)
  - July 1947-June 1950, 39 folders (Box 9)
  - July 1950-1953, 21 folders (Box 10)
  - 1954-January 1958, 31 folders (Box 11)
- Research for writings
  - Harry B. Hutchins biography
    - Correspondence 1943-1950, 8 folders (Box 12)
    - Collected materials (Box 12)
  - James B. Angell biography
    - Correspondence 1952-1955, 14 folders (Box 12)
  - Manuscripts of writings 1900-1915, undated, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Pere Marquette Building investment 1930-1940 (Box 12)
  - University of Toledo, consulting on its business operations 1946-1947, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - First Congregational Church of Ann Arbor correspondence and other papers 1924-1933, 4 folders (Box 12)
- Ann Arbor City Council 1945-1949
  - Public works 1942-1948 (Box 12)
  - Water Dept. 1944-1945 (Box 12)
  - Juvenile delinquency 1945 (Box 12)
  - Real estate 1945-1946 (Box 12)
  - Civic Center 1945-1946 (Box 12)
  - Pension plan for city employees 1945-1946, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Ways and Means Committee 1946 (Box 12)
  - City employee relations 1947 (Box 12)
  - Budget 1947 (Box 12)
  - City ordinances 1947-1948 (Box 13)
  - Parks and cemeteries 1947-1948 (Box 13)
  - City Council 1945-1948, 3 folders (Box 13)
- Papers (by date)
  - 1891-1957, 35 folders (Box 13)
    (these files contain much published materials, newsletters, catalogs, and other mailings)
- Personal and miscellaneous
  - University of Michigan student notebooks 1893-1897, 11 volumes (Box 14)
    (include notes on classes of Charles Horton Cooley, F. M. Taylor, Isaac Demmon, L. A. McLouth, Richard Hudson, Andrew McLaughlin, Henry Carter Adams, and B. A. Hinsdale)
  - University of Michigan and other essays (Box 14)
  - Scrapbook relating to University of Michigan, 1916-1922 (Box 15)
  - Diary detailing University of Michigan administrative meetings and business activities, 1926-1930 (Box 15)
  - Diary written while on a bicycle trip through Europe in 1896 entitled, "A Wheelman's Diary", typescript and photocopy of original (Box 15)
  - Account book listing poultry sales 1881-1890 (Box 15)
  - Letter of Julia Angell to Sara Browne Smith 1932 (Box 15)
  - Speeches undated, 1917-1953 (Box 15)
  - Obituaries and memorials for SWS (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
- Photographs
  - Album of unidentified portraits (Box 15)
  - Photographs of a locomotive owned by University of Michigan (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous; include portraits of Smith and his wife, Sara Browne Smith; group portrait of 1897 Michiganensian board; group portrait of University of Michigan students from Barry County, Michigan, 1894 photograph of employees of Hastings Wool Boot Company (Box 15)
Selective Index to Correspondents
This index lists some of the more significant corespondents in the chronologically arranged portion of the Correspondence series. It cites the correspondent and the date(s) of correspondence.
Abbot, Waldo, 1888-
May 4, 1936, May 8, 1948, Oct. 4, 1949
Adams, James P. (James Pickwell), 1895-1969.
Nov. 21, 1944, 1950
Adams, Randolph Greenfield, 1892-1951.
Nov. 4, 1940, Nov. 6, 1940, Jan. 23, 1947, Feb. 12, 1947, Sept. 16, 1949
Ainsworth, Arthur Sardius, 1862-
Apr. 7, 1911, July 7, 1933, July 12, 1933, July 19, 1933, Jan. 9, 1934, Feb. 15, 1934, Feb. 16, 1934, May 14, 1934, July 6, 1934, Aug. 2, 1935, May 12, 1936, Feb. 25, 1937, Mar. 8, 1937, May 6, 1937, May 8, 1937, Jan. 4, 1939
Dec. 1940, Dec. 26, 1941, Dec. 25, 1942, Oct. 31, 1943, Jan. 18, 1944, Nov. 21, 1944, Nov. 26, 1944, Dec. 25, 1944, Jan. 3, 1945, Jan. 10, 1945, Jan. 13, 1945, Dec. 10, 1945, Dec. 25, 1945, Jan. 14, 1948, Dec. 25, 1948, Dec. 27, 1948, Apr. 15, 1949, Dec. 25, 1949
Alger, Frederick Moulton, 1907-1967.
Oct. 6, 1947, Oct. 10, 1947
Allen, Frederick Lewis, 1890-1954.
Nov. 22, 1943
Anderson, Clinton Presba, 1895-
Oct. 6, 1947
Angell, Carleton Watson, 1887-1962.
May 27, 1928
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.
July 13, 1899, Feb. 15, 1900, July 19, 1900, Oct. 18, 1900
Angell, James Rowland, 1869-1949.
July 12, 1941, July 24, 1941, Mar. 9, 1942, Dec. 30, 1944, Dec. 27, 1946, Jan. 17, 1947, Jan. 30, 1947, Feb. 3, 1947
Angell, Robert Cooley, 1899-
Mar. 30, 1955
Anspach, Charles Le Roy, 1895-
May 1, 1948, May 17, 1954, May 13, 1955, May 8, 1956
Artiaga, Santiago, 1878-1962.
Nov. 27, 1927, Apr. 19, 1938, June 27, 1938, Dec. 27, 1941, Dec. 27, 1942, (not delivered), Nov. 20, 1945, Dec. 27, 1945, Feb. 1, 1946, Feb. 11, 1946, June 21, 1947, Dec. 15, 1947, Mar. 26, 1948, Apr. 10, 1948, Apr. 8, 1949, July 26, 1949, Oct. 24, 1949
Mar. 4, 1950, May 7, 1950, July 31, 1951, Feb. 3, 1952, Feb. 7, 1952, Apr. 11, 1952, July 9, 1953, Aug. 12, 1953, Oct. 24, 1953, Nov. 17, 1953, Jan. 6, 1954, Feb. 2, 1954, Feb. 9, 1954, Feb. 11, 1954, Feb. 17, 1954, Mar. 6, 1954, Oct. 18, 1954
Jan. 2, 1955, Jan. 31, 1955, Feb. 8, 1955, Mar. 8, 1955, Aug. 3, 1955, Aug. 30, 1955, Jan. 4, 1956, Jan. 10, 1956, Feb. 3. 1956, Mar. 6, 1956, Mar. 21, 1956, May 27, 1956, July 5, 1956, Aug. 7, 1956, Nov. 2, 1956, May 14, 1957, July 8, 1957, Sept. 7, 1957
Backus, Standish.
Mar. 26, 1927, Apr. 3, 1942
Bacon, Mark Reeves, 1852-1941.
Apr. 11, 1917, Apr. 14, 1917
Baird, Charles, 1870-1944.
July 24, 1908, Aug. 3, 1908, Dec. 31, 1941, Jan. 26, 1942
Baits, Vera Burridge, 1892-1963.
Nov. 15, 1944?, Nov. 13, 1946
Bald, F. Clever (Frederick Clever), 1897-1970.
Nov. 10, 1950, Nov. 12, 1957
Bates, Henry Moore, 1869-1949.
June 10, 1907, June 27, 1907, June 21, 1943, Aug. 21, 1957 [Mrs. H. M. Bates]
Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.
June 8, 1908, Nov. 4, 1910, Feb. 3, 1912, Oct. 21, 1934, Nov. 20, 1934, Aug. 24, 1935, July 27, 1936, Feb. 26, 1941
Bingay, Malcolm Wallace, 1884-
June 26, 1943, June 4, 1948, June 9, 1948, June 5, 1950, Jan. 20, 1951, Aug. 10, 1951, Aug. 15, 1952
Bishop, William Warner, 1871-1955.
Dec. 28, 1935, May 26, 1949
Boak, Arthur Edward Romilly, 1888-1962.
Sept. 7, 1944, Aug. 15, 1945
Bonisteel, Roscoe O. (Roscoe Osmond), 1888-
Nov. 10, 1936, Oct. 4, 1950, Mar. 20, 1951, Mar. 26, 1951, Mar. 9, 1953, .May 25, 1954
Boyles, Emerson R., 1881-1960.
Apr. 9, 1951
Bromage, Arthur W. (Arthur Watson), 1904-1979.
Apr. 25, 1945, Feb. 7, 1949
Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-1973.
Nov. 11, 1912, Feb. 14, 1937, Aug. 23, 1937, Apr. 15, 1938, .May 4, 1938, Nov. 14, 1938, July 1, 1942, July 26, 1942, July 28, 1942, Nov. 7, 1942, Nov. 14, 1942, Nov. 11, 1943, June 3, 1952, Dec. 18, 1953, Dec. 29, 1953, July 21, 1957, July 29, 1957
Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.
Dec. 31, 1930, Jan. 4, 1933
Brumm, John Lewis, 1878-1958.
May 17, 1945
Bulkley, Harry C. (Harry Conant), 1870-
May 28, 1912, Feb. 13, 1917
Burke, Edward Raymond, 1880-
Mar. 13, 1937, Mar. 19, 1937
Burke, George James, 1885-1950.
1940's
Burton, Clarence Monroe, 1853-1932.
May 18, 1902, Feb. 6, 1905, Feb. 11, 1905
Burton, Marion Le Roy, 1874-1925.
July 11, 1922, Jan. 29, 1923, Dec. 20, 1923, Dec. 29, 1923, Mar. 6, 1924, Mar. 26, 1924, Apr. 3, 1924, June 9, 1924, June 11, 1924
Carey, Henry Westronae, 1850-1911.
Jan. 10, 1910, Jan. 25, 1910, Jan. 26, 1910
Chandler, George Moseley.
July 19, 1908
Clements, William L. (William Lawrence), 1861-1934.
Aug.? 22, 1918, Mar. 23, 1919, Apr. 16, 1919, Mar. 4, 1920, July 25, 1920, Feb. 11, 1926, Apr. 22, 1931, May 2, 1933, July 14, 1934
Coller, Frederick A.
Aug. 5, 1957
Cook, Marshall L., 1858-1955.
May 3, 1895, Jan. 29, 1896, Oct. 12, 1902, Oct. 14, 1902, Oct. 17, 1902, Oct. 22, 1902, Oct. 7, 1903, Jan. 5, 1905, Feb. 14, 1907, July 16, 1908, Jan. 18, 1910, Dec. 21, 1924, Jan. 7, 1925, July 6, 1925, Jan. 26, 1926, July 7, 1926
June 20, 1927, June 29, 1927, Mar. 13, 1930, July 29, 1930, Nov. 19, 1930, Nov. 28, 1930, July 13, 1931, Nov. 24, 1931, Dec. 22, 1931, Apr. 22, 1932, Apr. 26, 1932, May 13, 1932, May 16, 1932, May 20, 1932, June 3, 1932, Oct. 11, 1932, 1933-1953
Cooley, Mortimer E. (Mortimer Elwyn), 1855-1944.
Dec. 7, 1931, Dec. 11, 1931, Mar. 28, 1934, Mar. 31, 1934, Jan. 14, 1935, Dec. 31, 1938, Feb. 4, 1939, Mar. 26, 1940, Dec. 30, 1940, Jan. 2, 1942, Apr. 23, 1942, Jan. 1, 1943, Apr. 13, 1943
Cowling, Donald J.
Mar. 16, 1925, Mar. 20, 1925, Mar. 25, 1925, Apr. 1, 1925
Craig, James Alexander, 1855-1932.
Feb. 16, 1897
Craig, Robert, 1882-1962.
Dec. 30, 1936
Cross, Arthur Lyon, 1873-1940.
Nov. 28, 1930, May 3, 1940
Curtiss, Mary Louise Welton.
Mar. 31, 1930
Davis, Calvin Olin, 1871-
Apr. 2, 1945, July 9, 1945, Jan. 9, 1946, Jan. 12, 1946, June 3, 1946
Davis, Joseph Baker, 1845-1920.
Mar. 14, 1901, June 2, 1910
Day, Edmund Ezra, 1883-1951.
Oct. 9, 1947, Oct. 11, 1947, Apr. 26, 1949
DeFoe, Murl Holcomb, 1879-
Jan. 30, 1922, Dec. 17, 1930, May 23, 1931, Feb. 20, 1933, Feb. 23, 1933, Feb. 27, 1933, Mar. 2, 1933, Mar. 3, 1933, July 26, 1933, Mar. 12, 1935, Mar. 14, 1935, Jan. 1936, June 29, 1939, July 17, 1939, Jan. 15, 1940, Mar. 6, 1940, May 29
1944, Dec. 19, 1944, Apr. 30, 1948, May 19, 1950, Aug. 15, 1951, Jan. 2, 1952, May 7, 1954, Mar. 11, 1955, June 2, 1956
Demmon, Isaac Newton, 1842-1920.
July 15, 1898, July 22, 1898, Aug. 4, 1898, May 13, 1899, Mar. 10, 1905
Densmore, Gail Ernest, 1894-
Feb. 18, 1939, Sept. 23, 1954
Doan, Leland Ira, 1894-1974.
Nov. 2, 1952, Nov. 5, 1952, Nov. 7, 1952
Dolph, Ray A.
Jan. 1932, July 28, 1934
Douglas, Lloyd C. (Lloyd Cassel), 1877-1951.
Feb. 2, 1920, Nov. 28, 1921, Dec. 20, 1921, Dec. 22, 1921, Feb. 28, 1923, Mar. 5, 1923, Feb. 24, 1925, Nov. 22, 1929, Apr. 17, 1930, Aug. 25, 1930, Oct. 13, 1931, Oct. 27, 1931
Nov. 27, 1931, Feb. 21, 1933, Mar. 3, 1933, Oct. 13, 1933, Oct. 23, 1933, Dec. 23, 1933?, Oct. 14, 1935, Oct. 27, 1935, 1938-1950, Jan. 19, 1951
Dumond, Dwight Lowell, 1895-
Aug. 2, 1938, Aug. 6, 1938
Eccles, Marriner S. (Marriner Stoddard), 1890-1977.
Apr. 3, 1943, Apr. 6, 1943
Effinger, John Robert, 1869-1933.
July 27, 1908
Elliott, Eugene Bradley, 1896-
Oct. 27, 1939, Dec. 20, 1939, Dec. 27, 1939
Emmons, H. H. (Harry H.)
Apr. 20, 1949, Apr. 24, 1949, May 20, 1949
Engel, Albert Joseph, 1888-1959.
May 24, 1931, Aug. 14, 1931, Aug. 19, 1931
Fairlie, John A. (John Archibald), 1872-1947.
Nov. 8, 1932
Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.
June 5, 1945, June 7, 1945, Feb. 11, 1947, Feb. 18, 1947, Jan. 3, 1948, Jan. 8, 1943, Feb. 3, 1950, Feb. 13, 1950, Aug. 16, 1950, Aug. 22, 1950, Mar. 4, 1952, Mar. 11, 1952
Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.
Nov. 28, 1934, Feb. 1, 1936, Apr. 27, 1938, May 13, 1938
Fitzpatrick, Keene, 1865-1944.
Nov. 10, 1931
Ford, Edsel, 1893-1943.
Sept. 20, 1934, Jan. 7, 1926, Dec. 10, 1927
Fosdick, Harry Emerson, 1878-1969.
Nov. 4, 1951, Nov. 3, 1951, Nov. 16, 1951
Foss, Sam Walter, 1858-1911.
Dec. 28, 1896
Frank, Coleman Dudley, 1876-1954.
Oct. 31, 1908, Nov. 3, 1908, Jan. 3, 1937, Jan. 9, 1937
Frayer, William Alley.
Dec. 31, 1931, Dec. 16, 1936
Fuller, Oramel B., 1858.
June 9, 1922, Oct. 2, 1922, Nov. 16, 1932
Furstenberg, Albert Carl, 1890-1969.
June 19, 1934, Apr. 2, 1935, May 26, 1935, Jan. 3, 1939, Dec. 26, 1939, Dec. 26, 1940, May 7, 1941, Dec. 28, 1942, Apr. 12, 1943, Apr. 28, 1943, Oct. 5, 1943, Dec. 27, 1943, June 3, 1944, Dec. 27, 1944
May 26, 1945, June 3, 1946, Dec. 26, 1946, Dec. 26, 1947, May 26, 1948, Sept. 28, 1948, Dec. 22, 1948, Dec. 23, 1950, Dec. 22, 1951, Dec. 22, 1952, Dec. 28, 1953
Gayley, Charles Mills, 1858-1932.
Dec. 4, 1904, July 27, 1909, July 29, 1909, Sept. 28, 1921, Nov. 1, 1925
George, Walter F. (Walter Franklin), 1878-1957.
June 14, 1943
Goddard, Edwin C. (Edwin Charles), 1865-1942.
May 7, 1937, May 11, 1937, Dec. 20, 1937
Gomberg, Moses, 1866-1947.
Jan. 28, 1936
Goodrich, Francis Lee Dewey, 1877-1962.
Aug. 24, 1934, Sept. 10, 1934, May 30, 1935, Mar. 2, 1936, Mar. 5, 1936, May 4, 1945, Feb. 27, 1949, Mar. 2, 1949, Apr. 15, 1952
Gore, Victor M.
Apr. 18, 1925, July 2, 1927, Aug. 24, 1930, Sept. 10, 1931, Sept. 17, 1938, Oct. 8, 1938
Graham, Frank Porter, 1886-
Sept. 27, 1947
Grant, Claudius Buchanan, 1835-1921.
Jan. 13, 1905, Jan. 24, 1905, Feb. 6, 1905
Green, Fred Warren, 1872-1936.
Apr. 6, 1928
Griffin, Clare E. (Clare Elmer), 1892-
May 1, 1942, May 2, 1942
Groesbeck, Alexander J., 1873-1953.
Dec. 30, 1924
Guest, Edgar A. (Edgar Albert), 1881-1959.
July 6, 1954, July 12, 1954
Haber, William, 1899-1988.
Oct. 18, 1950
Hanchett, Benjamin Sawtell, 1868-1933.
Jan. 16, 1912, Apr. 19, 1912, Dec. 31, 1912, June 28, 1927, Dec. 13, 1928, Feb. 6, 1932
Harriman, Karl Edwin, 1875-1935.
1904-1905
Hatcher, Harlan Henthorne, 1898-